<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Falafel</title>
    <link>https://falafel.haus/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Falafel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://falafel.haus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Working Group on NIH DMSP Guidance</title>
      <link>https://falafel.haus/project/wg_dmsp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falafel.haus/project/wg_dmsp/</guid>
      <description>About     This working group is a community effort to create resources to share with the researcher community in regards to the NIH Data Management and Sharing Policy (2023).
Materials, the list of contributors, and more can be found at the project website on OSF.
Acknowledgments     This project was made possible with support from the RDAP Association. The content is solely the responsibility of the authors and does not necessarily represent the official views of the RDAP association.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning for Open Grants</title>
      <link>https://falafel.haus/project/open_grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falafel.haus/project/open_grants/</guid>
      <description>About     This IMLS-funded project explores the potential for an open repository of funding proposals to elevate their recognition as scholarly products, improve access for the public and other grant seekers, and bring transparency to this facet of the research process.
This site builds on the longstanding OGrants project, led by Ethan White, to document a new phase of discussion, needs assessment, and technical planning for a repository of open grants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A campfire</title>
      <link>https://falafel.haus/talk/campfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falafel.haus/talk/campfire/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to give this talk! Stay tuned for video and slides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A seedling</title>
      <link>https://falafel.haus/talk/second-seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:15:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falafel.haus/talk/second-seedling/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A seedling</title>
      <link>https://falafel.haus/talk/seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 14:15:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falafel.haus/talk/seedling/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways to Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://falafel.haus/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falafel.haus/contact/</guid>
      <description>Inclusion Rider     For invited engagements, please note that I use the following inclusion rider.
I strive for events where the invited [speakers/panelists/etc] are representative of the diversity (along whichever axes) of the appropriate audience. If your event has not yet considered inclusive representation or you feel that there are improvements to be made, I would be happy to step down and/or suggest alternative speakers.
Email     UF: haoye@ufl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://falafel.haus/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falafel.haus/license/</guid>
      <description>All website content is shared under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License. Technical aspects of the website are derived from the Hugo Apéro theme.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://falafel.haus/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://falafel.haus/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Philosophy     I strive to make my teaching accessible and actionable, through setting expectations up front, and developing content and exercises that center learning.
My formal training comes from:
 &amp;ldquo;Teaching + Learning at the College Level&amp;rdquo;, a course on evidence-based teaching practices taught by UCSD&amp;rsquo;s Teaching + Learning Commons. (The course is now called &amp;ldquo;Introduction to College Teaching&amp;rdquo;.) The Carpentries Instructor Training and Trainer Training.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
